class Dummydb {
  List<Map<String, dynamic>> questions = [
  {
    "Question": "What is Flutter?",
    "Options": ["A programming language", "A framework for mobile development", "A database management tool", "A game engine"],
    "Answerindex": 1,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which programming language is used for developing Flutter applications?",
    "Options": ["JavaScript", "Python", "Dart", "Java"],
    "Answerindex": 2,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which widget is used to create a scrollable list of items in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["ListView", "Column", "Row", "Stack"],
    "Answerindex": 0,
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you add a floating action button to a Flutter application?",
    "Options": ["Using FAB widget", "Using Button widget", "Using FloatingActionButton widget", "Using ActionButton widget"],
    "Answerindex": 2,
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the purpose of the pubspec.yaml file in a Flutter project?",
    "Options": ["To define the project's dependencies", "To write the project's main code", "To manage database connections", "To design the user interface"],
    "Answerindex": 0,
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you run a Flutter app on a connected device?",
    "Options": ["flutter start", "flutter run", "flutter build", "flutter execute"],
    "Answerindex": 1,
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the purpose of the State class in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["To manage app's state", "To build the widget tree", "To handle user input", "To define app's routes"],
    "Answerindex": 0,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which method is used to update the state of a StatefulWidget in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["updateState()", "setState()", "changeState()", "modifyState()"],
    "Answerindex": 1,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which widget is used for aligning widgets within a container in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["Align", "Center", "Container", "Positioned"],
    "Answerindex": 1,
  },
  {
    "Question": "How do you create a horizontal divider in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["Using Divider widget", "Using HorizontalDivider widget", "Using Line widget", "Using Separator widget"],
    "Answerindex": 0,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which widget is used to display images in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["Img", "Picture", "Photo", "Image"],
    "Answerindex": 3,
  },
  {
    "Question": "What is the purpose of the main() function in a Flutter app?",
    "Options": ["To initialize the app", "To define the app's layout", "To handle user input", "To manage app's data"],
    "Answerindex": 0,
  },
  {
    "Question": "Which widget is used to handle tap gestures in Flutter?",
    "Options": ["TapWidget", "GestureDetector", "TouchListener", "TapHandler"],
    "Answerindex": 1,
  },
];

final List number=[1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13];

}